Hashem Al-Saqqa

+972592989725 | hashem.b.saqqa@gmail.com | Gaza

Summary

Android development expert with technical skills in gathering system requirements and logical data. I have a very strong knowledge of API. I have built multiple Applications using java, Kotlin, and UI/UX designs. With such strong knowledge in my career, I am dedicated, People-focused, and detail-oriented, a hard worker, and a responsible person, and have a stable, personal life, and learn incredibly quickly.

Experience

University College of Applied Sciences | Gaza Teacher Assistance in computer engineering | 02/2022 - Present

Freelancer | Gaza Android Developer | 04/2019 - Present

UNRWA - KYTC | Gaza Technical Trainer - Mobile development | 03/2022 - 08/2022

Skills

Android, Java, Kotlin, Restful API, Firebase, SQLite, Postman, Material Design, GitHub, Google Maps, Notifications, Responsive layout for different screens, Extracting design from XD or PSD file, Room database, project analysis

Education

Islamic University of Gaza | Gaza Master - Data Science | 11/2023

Islamic University of Gaza | Gaza Computer Science | 07/2021